the PC fund carbon x 2000 is a top of
its class high performance budget
fishing reel coming in at 80 this reel
has honestly surprised the heck out of
me it seems to be a high quality reel
that could be used for competitive
fishing and honestly is available for
just about anybody because of the low
price of eighty dollars one thing that's
super nice about this reel is it
actually comes in five different sizes
so there's a five hundred one thousand
two thousand three thousand four
thousand sized reel now this one that I
picked up is a 2000 which is honestly
just a great all-around reel
um like I said it has 22 pounds of drag
which is honestly pretty great I mean
that's something that you'll find in a
higher end fishing reel I mean you can
really crank in some big fish with that
much drag so pretty impressive there and
honestly my expectations have been met
with this thing it is super super fun to
use super fun to cast with one of my
favorite Parts is the drag
that clicking sound just sounds so cool
when you're reeling in a fish I can't
say good enough things about it this
reel is made with a carbon fiber body
and has a lot of stainless steel
components so it's never going to rust
or Decay or anything like that which is
super super nice and notable because a
lot of reels just won't last you a long
time but I believe that this PC fund
carbon ax 2000 is going to last the test
of time I mean it's made from quality
components and even at the coming in at
the price of a budget it's you know
budget real it's honestly not really a
budget reel it's kind of more so of a
higher end reel they just found out a
way to you know make it affordable for
everybody which is super cool the gear
ratio on this reel is a six two one now
if you go to different sizes those may
vary a little bit I think they have a
five two one and a six two one but all
around pretty much that's pretty
standard I would say but it works really
really well I wouldn't probably change
anything about about the gear ratio I do
like that another thing I wanted to go
over with you guys is just how well this
thing casts it's super smooth when you
cast it and there's never any problems I
mean it's always just every cast just
seems to be about the same as the last
one which is super nice you can get a
lot of distance on your cast which is
super important to me because a lot of
the times you know I'll fish with like a
weightless senko or you know just Texas
rigs especially in the summertime and on
a lot of reels it can be kind of hard to
get some distance on it but with this
thing you can really move that thing out
there which is super nice that's
probably the the casting is honestly
probably one of my favorite Parts about
this reel because you know you can
really whip that thing out there and you
don't have to worry about it sticking or
knocking or you know knocking your lure
off or anything like that it just works
great every single time which
honestly is a major selling point to me
because you know typically when you buy
like a you know lower priced reel you
never really know the quality until you
actually use it and you know sometimes
you can be a little bit skeptical but
with this I can tell you with 100
certainty that it is absolutely worth it
I also did want to mention if you guys
like these product reviews make sure you
subscribe to the channel because we have
a lot of product reviews on fishing
reels and fishing equipment here to come
so make sure you're subscribed let's get
back to the action another great part
about this reel is it sits in your hand
really really nicely it's not overly
bulky or anything like that so you can
fish with it really really well because
it's just designed I feel like to fit
into your hand perfectly the Eva handle
is super thick so that it really get a
good grip on it you don't have to worry
about your fingers slipping off of it or
anything like that and this reel is
super sturdy we're going to crank this
drag down so that when we get a fish you
guys can see just how well it pulls them
out of the water
a few moments later
there's a fish oh yeah oh it's a good
one come on get them on
get out of the weeds come on oh he came
oh no he's still on there what do we got
little Bass
with some salad oh gosh did you guys see
how well I could pull him on top of the
water I mean the drag is just perfect
um that was even with some weeds you
know so that adds probably a
a little bit of weight not the biggest
bass we're looking for but I mean we'll
take it and as you can see I mean the
Reel just did a great job I mean
obviously caught the fish and everything
to be expected so that's always super
super good to see I also should mention
how smooth it is when you reel it in I
mean straight out of the box it doesn't
need oil or anything it's just 100
percent ready to go which is super nice
because a lot of times in my experience
on the cheaper and reels you gotta you
really gotta oil them up you know if you
buy a reel under 100 bucks a lot of the
times it just needs oil which isn't a
big deal but with this one it really
just seems like they put the time and
effort into the quality of the Reel so
that you know everybody can afford a
higher end you know spinning reel which
is super nice can't say good enough
things about PC fun they seem to be a
top-notch company and I really think
they're making a name for themselves I'm
super excited to try some of their other
products this is the first reel I've
gotten from these guys and I can't wait
to try some more but all in all guys
that's going to wrap things up for us
today and as you guys can see the PC
fund carbon x 2000 is a top of its class
reel and I definitely can't say good
enough things about it if you guys are
looking at buying one of these go to
pcfun.com and use my code jj15 to get 15
off of whatever purchase you make and I
hope you guys enjoyed the video if you
did enjoy these product review videos
make sure you subscribe to the channel
and like the video and we'll see you
guys in the next one peace